Abdullah Ansari

Front-end Developer

Summary

I recently completed a 1-year **MERN Stack Web Development**Diploma at **Saylani Mass I.T Training Institute**, gaining hands-on experience. Additionally, I recently completed a 3-month unpaid front-end internship at **Saylani Mass I.T Training Institute** and a 2-month paid internship at **WP Coders Ltd**.

Experience

Digital Marketing

AR Software Agency Aug 2022 to Nov 2022

Front end Developer (Unpaid Internship)

Saylani Mass I.T Institute Nov 2022 to Jan 2023

Front end Developer (Paid Internship)

WP Coders Itd
Mar 2023 to June 2023
(Present)

Worked **remotely** as a Digital Marketing Specialist at **AR Software Agency** for 3 months.

Completed a **3-month unpaid internship** as a Front-end developer at **Saylani Mass I.T Training Institute**.

Front End Developer Paid Internship at WP Coders Ltd (ongoing, 3 months).

Education

Matric - Science BSEK

2019 to 2020

Intermediate (Commerce) BIEK

2021 to 2022

Virtual University - BSCS

2023 - Current(1st Year)

Saylani Mass I.T Training Institute

MERN Stack 1 Year Diploma 2022

Skills

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT (ES6), **REACTJS and REDUX**, Wordpress, REACT-NATIVE, BOOTSTRAP, FIREBASE, NODEJS, EXPRESSJS, MONGODB, GITHUB

Contact



+92 316 0120286



www.abdullahansari.web.app



abdullah.tariq.ansariata @gmail.com



Surjani Town, Sector 7-D, Karachi